Guide to the Darrin Zammit Lupi photojournalism archive, 2004-2017 RL.11613
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- On Board the Aquarius, 2017 December 15-19; 1.5 Linear Feet 1 box 20 photographic prints; 16.73 Gigabytes 3210 files (110 tiff, 3035 jpg, 46 png, 11 mp4, 3 pdf, 2 doc, 1 VLC, 1 txt, and 1 xls)
  - TIFF images (electronic files), 2017 December 15-19; 110 files (.tif); 11.4 GB
    - Migrants transferred from Open Arms 1, 2017 December 16 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0038)
      Migrants arrive on the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, after a mid-sea transfer from MV Open Arms, the search and rescue ship of Proactiva Open Arms, in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 16, 2017. 154 migrants were transferred to the Aquarius from Open Arms, bringing the total on board to 320. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrants transferred from Open Arms 2, 2017 December 16 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0039)
    - Migrants watch new arrivals, 2017 December 16 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0040)
      Migrants on the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, look at new arrivals on the ship after a mid-sea transfer from MV Open Arms, the search and rescue ship of Proactiva Open Arms, in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 16, 2017. 154 migrants were transferred to the Aquarius from Open Arms, bringing the total on board to 320. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrant sits on staircase, 2017 December 16 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0041)
      A migrant sits at the top of a staircase on the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 16, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrants transferred from Open Arms 3, 2017 December 16 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0042)
    - Migrants transferred from Open Arms 4, 2017 December 16 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0043)
    - Migrant drinks fruit juice, 2017 December 16 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0044)
      A migrant drinks from a fruit juice carton on the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 16, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrant reacts, 2017 December 16 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0045)
      A migrant reacts on the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 16, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrants with baby in RHIB, 2017 December 16 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0046)
      Migrants, including a baby, sit in a rigid hulled inflatable boat (RHIB) from MV Open Arms, the search and rescue ship of Proactiva Open Arms, as it arrives alongside MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, during a mid-sea transfer of migrants in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 16, 2017. 154 migrants were transferred to the Aquarius from Open Arms, bringing the total on board to 320. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrant baby brought to Aquarius 1, 2017 December 16 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0047)
      A crew member of MV Open Arms, the search and rescue ship of Proactiva Open Arms, passes a migrant baby to crew members of MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, during a mid-sea transfer of migrants in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 16, 2017. 154 migrants were transferred to the Aquarius from Open Arms, bringing the total on board to 320. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrant baby brought to Aquarius 2, 2017 December 16 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0048)
      Crew members of MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, remove a life jacket from a migrant baby during a mid-sea transfer of migrants from MV Open Arms, the search and rescue ship of Proactiva Open Arms, in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 16, 2017. 154 migrants were transferred to the Aquarius from Open Arms, bringing the total on board to 320. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrant baby brought to Aquarius 3, 2017 December 16 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0049)
      A crew member of MV Open Arms, the search and rescue ship of Proactiva Open Arms, carries a migrant baby before passing it to crew members of MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, during a mid-sea transfer of migrants in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 16, 2017. 154 migrants were transferred to the Aquarius from Open Arms, bringing the total on board to 320. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrants rest on Aquarius 1, 2017 December 16 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0050)
      Migrants rest on the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 16, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrant sits with her children, 2017 December 17 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0051)
      A migrant sits with her children on the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, as it makes its way to the Italian island of Sicily after rescue operations in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 17, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrants rest on Aquarius 2, 2017 December 17 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0052)
      Migrants rest on the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, as it makes its way to the Italian island of Sicily after rescue operations in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 17, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrants rest on Aquarius 3, 2017 December 17 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0053)
    - Migrants rest on Aquarius 4, 2017 December 17 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0054)
      Migrants rest on the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, as it passes the Maltese island of Gozo while making its way to the Italian island of Sicily after rescue operations in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 17, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrant stands on deck, 2017 December 17 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0055)
      A migrant stands on the deck of the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, as it passes the Maltese island of Gozo while making its way to the Italian island of Sicily after rescue operations in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 17, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrant takes selfie, 2017 December 17 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0056)
      A migrant takes a selfie on the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, as it makes its way to the Italian island of Sicily after rescue operations in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 17, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrant looks out to sea 2, 2017 December 17 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0057)
      A migrant looks out to sea on the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, as it makes its way to the Italian island of Sicily after rescue operations in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 17, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrants rest on Aquarius 5, 2017 December 17 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0058)
    - Migrants look out to sea 2, 2017 December 17 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0059)
      Migrants look out to sea on the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, as it makes its way to the Italian island of Sicily after rescue operations in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 17, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrants look out to sea 3, 2017 December 17 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0060)
    - Migrants rest on Aquarius 6, 2017 December 17 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0061)
      Migrants rest on the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, as it approaches the Italian island of Sicily after rescue operations in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 17, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrant prays, 2017 December 17 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0062)
      A migrant prays on the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, as it approaches the Italian island of Sicily after rescue operations in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 17, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrant walks along deck, 2017 December 17 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0063)
      A migrant walks along the deck of the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, as it approaches the Italian island of Sicily after rescue operations in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 17, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrants rest on Aquarius 7, 2017 December 17 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0064)
    - Migrant climbs down stairs, 2017 December 17 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0065)
      A migrant climbs down a staircase on the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, as it approaches the Italian island of Sicily after rescue operations in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 17, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrant rests 1, 2017 December 17 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0066)
      A migrant rests on the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, as it approaches the Italian island of Sicily after rescue operations in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 17, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrant holds onto rope, 2017 December 17 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0067)
      A migrant holds a rope to keep his balance on the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, as it approaches the Italian island of Sicily after rescue operations in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 17, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrant rests 2, 2017 December 17 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0068)
    - Migrant queues for meal, 2017 December 17 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0069)
      A migrant queues to collect his evening meal on the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, as it approaches the Italian island of Sicily after rescue operations in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 17, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrants queue for meal 1, 2017 December 17 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0070)
      Migrants queue to collect their evening meal on the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, as it approaches the Italian island of Sicily after rescue operations in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 17, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrant children help distribute meals 1, 2017 December 17 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0071)
      Migrant children help distribute evening meals on the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, as it approaches the Italian island of Sicily after rescue operations in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 17, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrant children help distribute meals 2, 2017 December 17 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0072)
    - Migrants queue for meal 2, 2017 December 17 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0073)
    - Migrants sit, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0074)
      Migrants sit on the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, as it approaches Pozzallo on Italian island of Sicily after rescue operations in the central Mediterranean off the coast of Libya, December 18, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrants wait on Aquarius off Pozzallo 1, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0075)
      Migrants wait for the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, to enter Pozzallo on the island of Sicily, Italy, December 18, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrants wait on Aquarius off Pozzallo 2, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0076)
      A migrant waits for the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, to enter Pozzallo on the island of Sicily, Italy, December 18, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrants wait on Aquarius off Pozzallo 3, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0077)
    - Migrants wait on Aquarius off Pozzallo 4, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0078)
    - Migrants wait on Aquarius off Pozzallo 5, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0079)
    - Migrants wait on Aquarius off Pozzallo 6, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0080)
    - Migrant washes his face, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0081)
      A migrant washes his face while waiting for the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, to enter Pozzallo on the island of Sicily, Italy, December 18, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrants wait on Aquarius off Pozzallo 7, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0082)
    - Migrants wait on Aquarius off Pozzallo 8, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0083)
    - Migrants wait on Aquarius off Pozzallo 9, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0084)
    - Migrants wait on Aquarius off Pozzallo 10, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0085)
    - Migrants wait on Aquarius off Pozzallo 11, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0086)
    - Migrants wait on Aquarius off Pozzallo 12, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0087)
    - Migrants wait on Aquarius off Pozzallo 13, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0088)
    - Migrants look on as Aquarius reaches Pozzallo 1, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0089)
      Migrants look on as the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, enters Pozzallo on the island of Sicily, Italy, December 18, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrants sing and dance 1, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0090)
      Migrants sing and dance as the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, enters Pozzallo on the island of Sicily, Italy, December 18, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrants sing and dance 2, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0091)
    - Migrants look on as Aquarius reaches Pozzallo 2, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0092)
    - Migrant child reacts, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0093)
      A migrant child reacts while looking through a porthole as the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, enters Pozzallo on the island of Sicily, Italy, December 18, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrant child looks through porthole, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0094)
      A migrant child looks through a porthole as the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, enters Pozzallo on the island of Sicily, Italy, December 18, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrants react as Aquarius reaches Pozzallo, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0095)
      Migrants react while looking through portholes as the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, enters Pozzallo on the island of Sicily, Italy, December 18, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrants wait to disembark 1, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0096)
      A migrant waits on the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, after it arrived in Pozzallo on the island of Sicily, Italy, December 18, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrant children wait, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0097)
      Migrant children wait on the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, after it arrived in Pozzallo on the island of Sicily, Italy, December 18, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrant child plays with health officer, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0098)
      A migrant child plays with an Italian public health official on the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, after it arrived in Pozzallo on the island of Sicily, Italy, December 18, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrants wait to disembark 2, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0099)
      Migrants wait to disembark from the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, after it arrived in Pozzallo on the island of Sicily, Italy, December 18, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrants wait to disembark 3, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0100)
    - Migrants wait to disembark 4, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0101)
    - Migrants wait to disembark 5, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0102)
    - Migrants wait to disembark 6, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0103)
    - Italian soldiers near medical tent, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0104)
      Italian soldiers stand near a medical tent for migrants after the migrants disembarked from the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, in Pozzallo on the island of Sicily, Italy, December 18, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrant reacts while waiting to disembark 1, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0105)
      A migrant reacts while waiting to disembark from the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, after it arrived in Pozzallo on the island of Sicily, Italy, December 18, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrants disembark, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0106)
      Migrants disembark from the MV Aquarius, a search and rescue ship run in partnership between SOS Méditeranée and Médecins sans Frontières, after it arrived in Pozzallo on the island of Sicily, Italy, December 18, 2017. Photo: Darrin Zammit Lupi
    - Migrants wait to disembark 7, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0107)
    - Migrants wait to disembark 8, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0108)
    - Migrant reacts while waiting to disembark 2, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0109)
    - Migrants wait to disembark 9, 2017 December 18 (Digital-materials RL11613-SET-0001, Image-file RL.11613-TIFF-0110)
  - Large photographic prints, 2017 December 15-18; 20 prints 1 box 20x24 inches
    Comprises 20 color inkjet prints, selected by the photographer Darrin Zammit Lupi from the thousands of digital photographs he took while on board an Italian rescue ship in the Mediterranean. The prints measure approximately 20x24 inches.
    Digital images of these prints are immediately available in this collection guide, via links in the tiffs format series. There are also low-resolution images and contact sheets with related images available; these are only accessible onsite, in the Rubenstein Library reading room.
    - Rescue at sea 3, 2017 December 15 (Box 1, Image RL.11613-P-0001)
    - Migrants await rescue 3, 2017 December 15 (Box 1, Image RL.11613-P-0002)
    - Migrants on Italian RHB 1, 2017 December 15 (Box 1, Image RL.11613-P-0003)
    - Migrants embrace, 2017 December 15 (Box 1, Image RL.11613-P-0004)
    - Migrants queue for registration, 2017 December 15 (Box 1, Image RL.11613-P-0005)
    - Migrants talk 1, 2017 December 16 (Box 1, Image RL.11613-P-0006)